

CONTACT



336-829-8283



meghankcombs@gmail.com



Clemmons, NC



Linkedin.com/in/meghankcombs

EDUCATION

MASTER'S DEGREE
Art History-Museum Studies
CUNY City College
2010 -2013

BACHELOR'S DEGREE Art History & Criticism UNC Greensboro 2007 - 2009

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

C#, ASP.NET, MVC, SQL

JavaScript, jQuery

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap

PERSONAL

Creative Thinker

Project Management

MEGHAN COMBS

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE

In 2017, I migrated from the art world to the tech field. While transitioning, my creative background, critical evaluation skills, and project management experience helped me quickly expand my knowledge of web development. This makes me an ideal candidate for Full-Stack positions, which require logic based back-end development and creative front-end design.

EXPERIENCE

C#/.NET DEVELOPER | CODER FOUNDRY

October 2017 - present

I designed and developed five MVC projects:

- A Portfolio site using HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and jQuery.
- A Blog and Shopping Cart application, which implemented Code First Migrations using LINQ and Entity Framework to create the databases.
- A multi-functional Issue Tracker (Kink Fix) with enhanced roles and security, which also used a Code First Relational database designed in SQL Server.
- A Financial Portal created via a Database First Approach that models popular software such as QuickBooks.

Portfolio site: http://mcombs-mvcportfolio.azurewebsites.net GitHub Repositories: github.com/meghankcombs

GALLERY & COLLECTION MANAGER | BLUMKA GALLERY

October 2015 - October 2017

This position required an abundance of initiative and the adoption of multiple roles. In keeping with this, I accomplished:

- Reimagining and rebuilding the website.
- Modernizing the database by researching leading industry software.
- Establishing the gallery's social media presence.
- Researching and implementing a Simple IRA for employees.
- Standardizing bookkeeping and database recording practices.

VISITOR SERVICES | RUBIN MUSEUM

October 2010 - May 2014

I began as a Visitor Attendant and was promoted to Visitor Experience Associate, then Volunteer Coordinator. My accomplishments were:

- Recruiting and supervising 50+ volunteers
- Streamlining and organizing the volunteer database
- Creating new volunteer tasks within museum departments